{
    "subject": "resource/Ian_Bruce_Ferguson",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Ian Bruce Ferguson",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Ian Bruce Ferguson is Ian Bruce Ferguson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854832887649536,
            "question": "What is the full name of Ian Bruce Ferguson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9780904054641724,
            "question": "Is 'Ian Bruce Ferguson' a common full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9771342873573303,
            "question": "Is Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name different from his given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9678892493247986,
            "question": "Are there any nicknames associated with Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9498446583747864,
            "question": "How many names are in Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9448756575584412,
            "question": "Does Ian Bruce Ferguson use his full name professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9246460199356079,
            "question": "What are all the parts of Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9239396452903748,
            "question": "What is unusual about Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9028362035751343,
            "question": "What is the order of Ian Bruce Ferguson's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8735347390174866,
            "question": "Could you find someone with the same first and middle name as Ian Bruce Ferguson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Ian Bruce Ferguson is Ian Bruce Ferguson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4758_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the order of Ian Bruce Ferguson's names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4758_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is unusual about Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4758_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are all the parts of Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4758_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4758_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe provided context information includes biographical details about a person named Ian Bruce Ferguson, which confirms that the full name \"Ian Bruce Ferguson\" is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}